### Privacy Statement

Your privacy is important to OpenTTD. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that OpenTTD collects, and the ways in which OpenTTD uses that personal information.

### Personal Information Collection

OpenTTD may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

* information that you provide for the purpose of registering with the website (GitHub username and user identifier);
* any other information that you send to OpenTTD.

### Using Personal Information

OpenTTD may use your personal information to enable your access to and use of the website services.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, OpenTTD may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

### Security of your Data

OpenTTD will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

OpenTTD will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

### Cross-border Data Transfers

Information that OpenTTD collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which OpenTTD operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the Internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

### Updating this Statement

OpenTTD may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

### Other Websites

This website contains links to other websites.

OpenTTD is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

### Contact OpenTTD

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or OpenTTD's treatment of your personal information, please write by email to [info@openttd.org](mailto:info@openttd.org).

### This Privacy Statement

This privacy statement is based on an original template created by [website-contracts.co.uk](http://website-contracts.co.uk/) and distributed by [freenetlaw.com](http://freenetlaw.com/).

### Cookies Policy

### About Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored in text files that are saved on your computer or other devices when websites are loaded in a browser. They are widely used to remember you and your preferences, either for a single visit (through a "session cookie") or for multiple repeat visits (using a "persistent cookie").

Session cookies are temporary cookies that are used during the course of your visit to the Website, and they expire when you close the web browser.

Persistent cookies are used to remember your preferences within our Website and remain on your desktop or mobile device even after you close your browser or restart your computer. They ensure a consistent and efficient experience for you while visiting the Website and Services.

(this text is based on an original template created by websitepolicies.com)

### Cookies on our Website

OpenTTD only uses session cookies, and only for the authenticated parts of some of our services (like our wiki, BaNaNaS, etc), so called "necessary cookies". These cookies are only set when you login to those services, and only restrict access to the authenticated part of those services.

The name of the cookie always starts with the name of the service (like "wiki" or "bananas") followed by "\_sid".

OpenTTD does not make use of any functional or any third party cookies.

Copyright © 2005-2024 OpenTTD Team
